<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome page | EN on Portfolio</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome page | EN on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:13:57 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Right Color</title>
      <link>/en/projets/therightcolor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:13:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/therightcolor/</guid>
      <description>I/ Application development with Angular To begin with, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at Angular. It&amp;rsquo;s a client-side framework based on Typescript. The special feature of this framework is its &amp;ldquo;SPA&amp;rdquo; for Single Page Applications aspect. So, our application is on a single web page. The primary aim is to avoid loading a new page, thereby enhancing the user experience.
II/ The goal of the game The objective is simple: to get the best score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Toile</title>
      <link>/en/projets/latoile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:22:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/latoile/</guid>
      <description>Project members : AMADOR Clara LinkedIn LEGRY Louis LinkedIn FERAUD Alexandre LinkedIn FISCHER Julien LinkedIn BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn SANTORO Thomas LinkedIn I/ Explore &amp;ldquo;La Toile&amp;rdquo;, our virtual exposition created in 48 hours This is our latest university project: &amp;ldquo;La Toile &amp;ldquo;, a virtual exhibition of digital images. We chose to represent this exhibition in the form of the Paris metro, with each room representing a metro stop. Our goal was to create this site in only 48 hours and we are proud to have successfully overcome this challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three-tier architecture application</title>
      <link>/en/projets/projetmsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:22:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/projetmsi/</guid>
      <description>Project members : BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn SANTORO Thomas LinkedIn I/ Implementation of the application using Flask So, the application was made with Flask, a micro framework for web development in Python.
We will build a web application based on a three-tier architecture.
The two-tier architecture characterises client/server systems in which the client requests a resource and the server provides it directly. This means that the server does not call on another application to provide the service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fractal project</title>
      <link>/en/projets/projetfractales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 17:22:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/projetfractales/</guid>
      <description>Project members : BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn SANTORO Thomas LinkedIn I/ Complex numbers In this section, we are asked to implement a class to perform classical operations on complex numbers. This class must implement the IComplex interface which is provided to us. A test class is also provided to check that our implementation is correct.
II/ Complex suites and fractals It is possible to generate nice fractals by considering sequences of complex numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Management Application</title>
      <link>/en/projets/appli_gestion_vente/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 19:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/appli_gestion_vente/</guid>
      <description>In this project, a sales management application was developed.
Part I In this first part, the realization of a sales management application without graphical interface is a requirement. This will allow us to use all our skills learned in Java.
Java So we had to make different packages:
The article package This one will allow the management of the articles present in our application.
The client package This one will allow the management of the customers present in our application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Expo</title>
      <link>/en/projets/dragon_expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/dragon_expo/</guid>
      <description>This is the first concrete project I have done in IT. In this project, the creation of an event company was required. In order to improve its communication, the creation of a website and its design was necessary.
I/ Creation of the company The first step of this project was to brainstorm to find out more about the type of event we were proposing. Once we found our theme, in this case an exposition about dragons, we made different personas to determine the potential targets of our company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24H INFO</title>
      <link>/en/evenements/24-hours-info-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/evenements/24-hours-info-2023/</guid>
      <description>The 2023 edition of the 24 hours of info took place in Bourg-en-Bresse, and was organized by the IUT Lyon 1 ! We were 23 teams in competition.
Membres de l&amp;rsquo;équipe : BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn FIEVET Arnaud LinkedIn I/ How did I discover this competition? During my computer science degree at the IUT of Lens, our web development teacher told us about this competition.
This year, I also had the opportunity to participate to the SWERC, a really memorable experience!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Fresk</title>
      <link>/en/benevolat/climate-fresk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/benevolat/climate-fresk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Symfony 5 by creating an e-commerce website</title>
      <link>/en/certifications/udemy-symfony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/certifications/udemy-symfony/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal notices : </title>
      <link>/en/legal-notices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/legal-notices/</guid>
      <description>In accordance with the provisions of Law No. 2004-575 of June 21, 2004 on confidence in the digital economy, users of the Portfolio website are informed of the identity of the various parties involved in its creation and monitoring.
Site Edition The present site, accessible at the URL aymericjak.github.io (the &amp;ldquo;Portfolio&amp;rdquo;), is edited by:
Aymeric JAKOBOWSKI, residing at 9 rue Angela Davis 62300 LENS, of French nationality (France), born on 09/13/2003,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My skills : </title>
      <link>/en/skills-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/skills-en/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pix certification</title>
      <link>/en/certifications/pix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/certifications/pix/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWERC</title>
      <link>/en/evenements/swerc-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/evenements/swerc-2023/</guid>
      <description>The 2023 edition of SWERC took place in Milan, Italy! We were 120 teams in competition.
Project members : FALQUE Thibault (coach) LinkedIn BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn FACON Nicolas LinkedIn I/ How did I discover this competition? During my computer science degree at the IUT of Lens, there were occasional SAE (Situation of Apprentice and Evaluation). In semester 3, our teacher decided to realize a small algorithmic competition between the different students of the promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
