<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web on Portfolio</title>
    <link>/en/categories/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:13:57 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/categories/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Right Color</title>
      <link>/en/projets/therightcolor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:13:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/therightcolor/</guid>
      <description>I/ Application development with Angular To begin with, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at Angular. It&amp;rsquo;s a client-side framework based on Typescript. The special feature of this framework is its &amp;ldquo;SPA&amp;rdquo; for Single Page Applications aspect. So, our application is on a single web page. The primary aim is to avoid loading a new page, thereby enhancing the user experience.
II/ The goal of the game The objective is simple: to get the best score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Toile</title>
      <link>/en/projets/latoile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:22:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/latoile/</guid>
      <description>Project members : AMADOR Clara LinkedIn LEGRY Louis LinkedIn FERAUD Alexandre LinkedIn FISCHER Julien LinkedIn BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn SANTORO Thomas LinkedIn I/ Explore &amp;ldquo;La Toile&amp;rdquo;, our virtual exposition created in 48 hours This is our latest university project: &amp;ldquo;La Toile &amp;ldquo;, a virtual exhibition of digital images. We chose to represent this exhibition in the form of the Paris metro, with each room representing a metro stop. Our goal was to create this site in only 48 hours and we are proud to have successfully overcome this challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three-tier architecture application</title>
      <link>/en/projets/projetmsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:22:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/projetmsi/</guid>
      <description>Project members : BOBEUF Jules LinkedIn SANTORO Thomas LinkedIn I/ Implementation of the application using Flask So, the application was made with Flask, a micro framework for web development in Python.
We will build a web application based on a three-tier architecture.
The two-tier architecture characterises client/server systems in which the client requests a resource and the server provides it directly. This means that the server does not call on another application to provide the service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Expo</title>
      <link>/en/projets/dragon_expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projets/dragon_expo/</guid>
      <description>This is the first concrete project I have done in IT. In this project, the creation of an event company was required. In order to improve its communication, the creation of a website and its design was necessary.
I/ Creation of the company The first step of this project was to brainstorm to find out more about the type of event we were proposing. Once we found our theme, in this case an exposition about dragons, we made different personas to determine the potential targets of our company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
